Stella's at the wheel, she's got the master plan
Cruisin' down the highway in a beat-up van
Luna's right beside me, knows my every move Got
the radio blasting a familiar groove The
windows down, the summer air is sweet Got the
whole world right here at our feet Just four best
friends against the setting sun Our real
adventure has just begun Yeah, we're chasing
the sun on this open road Got my guiding stars to
share the load An older sister, a twin, a brand
new friend A story that I hope will never end
We're nineteen and the world is ours to run Yeah,
we're chasing the sun
Olivia's laughing, a bright and brilliant
sound The greatest friend I've ever found She
sees the boy that's deep inside The one who has no
need to hide Three different lights that shine
as one Before the day is finally done We're
making memories fast and free. Just my guiding
stars and me. Yeah, we're chasing the sun on this
open road. Got my guiding stars to share the
load. An older sister, a twin, a brand new
friend. A story that I hope will never end. We're
19 and the world is ours to run. Yeah, we're
chasing the sun.
Okay.
Yeah, we're chasing the sun on this open road Got
my guiding stars to share the load An older
sister, a twin, a brand new friend A story that I
hope will never end We're nineteen and the world
is ours to run Yeah, we're chasing the sun